I am your maker.
（観察者）私が お前をつくった
We have a grand objective.
私たちには大いなる目的がある
To preserve this world.
この世界を保存することだ
And this entity was sent to this
world to impede our objective.
そして こいつは
その計画を阻むために
放り込まれた存在だ
Well, Fushi, we shall have fun.
ではフシ 楽しくやろう
Until the coming end.
きたる終わりの そのときまで
♪～
～♪
I've been thinking lately...
（グーグー）最近 思うんだ
Why am I me?
なんで僕は僕なんだろうって
Why wasn't I born to the family
in that mansion over there?
なんで あの屋敷の子供に
生まれなかったんだろうって
I feel that way, too.
（シン）俺も そう思うよ
That's why we brothers are working every day.
だから俺たち兄弟は
毎日こうして働いてる
Right?
だろ？
First, we're going to save up a ton of money.
まずはカネを たんまりためる
And then, someday, we can build a huge
house like that one to live in together.
そして いつか
あの家みたいな
デカい家を建てて２人で住もう
（グーグー）わあ…
The Boy Who Wants to Change
All right, time to work!
さあ 仕事だ！
Shin, you're on the fields today.
（チャンの父）
シン お前は今日も畑だ
Gugu, go sell vegetables at the market.
グーグーは市場で野菜を売れ
Sell every last one.
１つ残らず売ってこいよ
Yes, master.
（グーグー）はい 旦那さま！
Fresh produce here!
らっしゃい らっしゃい！
らっしゃい らっしゃい…
あっ
That girl's always here.
（グーグー）
あの子 いつも ここにいるな
I wonder what her name is.
何て名前だろ あの屋敷の子かな？
Maybe she's from that mansion?
ハッ
Do you sell seeds here?
（酒爺(さけじい)）ここは種は売っとるかね？
Huh?
Oh, no, I don't.
え？　あっ いいえ
売ってません
（イノブタの鳴き声）
I'll ask my master later.
あとで旦那さまに聞いておきます
Thank you. Bye, now.
（酒爺）ありがとう では！
That old fart's as weird as ever.
（店番）
相変わらずヘンな爺さんだな
You know him?
知ってるの？
He's the brewer who lives atop the hill.
（店番）丘の上の酒屋さ
（イノブタの鳴き声）
I heard he's involved in
some illegal business.
犯罪まがいの仕事をしてるって
ウワサだぜ
I'm home, Big Bro.
（グーグー）兄ちゃん ただいま
I got some leftovers from the others.
Later, Shin.
まかない もらったよ
（友人）じゃあな シン
You'd better win tomorrow.
（友人）明日は勝てよ
Yeah.
Bye.
（シン）おう また
Who were they?
（グーグー）誰？
My friends.
友達
I just got to know them recently.
最近 知り合ったんだ
Yeah?
（グーグー）ふーん…
Huh?
あれ…
There's some missing.
減ってる
Big Bro, did you use some money today?
兄ちゃん 今日 何かに使った？
Why would I do that?
んなわけ ねえだろ
There's a handful missing.
１束 少ないんだ 空き巣かな
Do you think we were robbed?
Those people didn't find
out about this, did they?
さっきの人たちには
見られてないよね？
Don't you accuse my friends.
俺の友達を疑うんじゃねえ！
R-Right. Sorry.
そ… そうだよね ごめんなさい
I just heard there was someone
sketchy in the neighborhood, so...
近所に物騒な人がいるって
聞いたから…
ああ…
I'm shocked, though.
でも本当にショックだ
What's lost is lost.
とられたもんは しかたねえ
ウジウジすんなって
Don't let it get to you.
Yeah, you're right.
うん そうだよね
We can just work some more
and make more money.
また働いて ためればいいだけだ
I'm going to hide it here from now on.
（グーグー）
隠し場所 ここに変えるよ
Okay.
（シン）ああ
Want half of the steamed bun I got?
（グーグー）もらってきた
おまんじゅう 半分 食べる？
No, thanks.
いらない
（グーグー）あ…
（ミール）キュウ キュウ…
What's up? Are you hungry?
何だ お前 腹減ってんのか？
Here, eat up.
ほら 食いな
Things suck for both of us, huh?
お互い つらいな
Fresh produce here!
らっしゃい らっしゃい！
（ミール）キュー！
（グーグー）わっ！
お前 昨日のヤツじゃないか
Hey, you're the dog from yesterday!
Sorry, I don't have any steamed buns today.
悪いな 今日は まんじゅう ないぞ
Meer?
ん？　“ミール”？
Your name's Meer, huh?
お前 ミールって名前なのか
Meer!
（リーン）ミール！
（グーグー）ん？
It's her!
（グーグー）あの子だ
Meer!
（リーン）ミール！
（ミールの鳴き声）
（グーグー）
あ… あ… あ… あの…
Um...
Is this who you're looking for?
捜してるの この子ですか？
え？　あっ！
Meer!
いやん ミール！
会いたかったわ！
I missed you!
I should thank you.
お礼をしないと…
これなんか どうかしら？
How about this?
That was a gift from your father, Miss.
（侍女）お嬢さま それは
お父さまからの贈り物ですよ
It's fine.
（グーグー）あっ…
（リーン）いいのよ
He bought it for me knowing
I don't wear this color.
私が こんな色つけないって
知ってるくせに買ってきたんだから
Sell this, and you won't have
to sell veggies ever again.
これを売れば野菜を売る仕事なんて
一生しなくて済むわよ
え！
She knew me!
僕のこと知ってたんだ
Um... What's your name?
あの… 君の名前は？
That was a rude thing to say to him.
（侍女）今の言葉は失礼ですよ
I was just trying to cheer him up.
（リーン）ええ？
励ましのつもりだったんだけどな
Oh...
あれ？
I'm home, Big Bro!
ただいま 兄ちゃん！
I had a good day today!
今日 いいことがあってさ…
ん？
Big Bro?
兄ちゃん？　兄ちゃん？
ん？
There's a thing called "fate" in this world.
（シン）
この世には運命って言葉がある
I've decided to fight against it.
俺は それに抗(あらが)うことにした
Sorry, Gugu.
ごめん グーグー
Liar.
（グーグー）ウソつき
フゥ…
Why am I me?
（グーグー）
なんで僕は僕なんだろう？
Sell this, and you won't have
to sell veggies ever again.
（リーン）これを売れば
野菜を売る仕事なんて
一生しなくて済むわよ
（トロッコが走る音）
ん？
If I crashed into that thing...
あれに ぶつかれば
ドーンガラガラガシャーンって
Like, bam! Tumble! Crash!
Would it change my fate?
運命 変わらないかな…
Nah, what the heck am I thinking?
って 何バカなこと
考えてるんだ 僕は…
Hey! Are you all right?
（運転手）おーい ケガないか？
ハァハァ… せえの！
One, two...
うう…
It won't budge.
チッ ビクともしねえ
I gotta go get some help.
Could you keep an eye on this?
人呼んでくるから
見ててくれねえか？
Huh? Oh...
（グーグー）え？　あ…
（運転手の荒い息）
（グーグー）ハァ…
That was dangerous. He was going too fast.
危ないな スピード出しすぎだよ
I actually would've died.
本当に死ぬところだった
ん？
Hey!
おーい！　そこの人 危ないよ！
You there! Look out!
ああ！
Look out!
危ないよ！　逃げて！
Run!
（リーン）キャッ…
あ…
Somebody... help me...
誰か助けて…
（丸太が落ちる音）
She's bleeding!
（運転手）
血が出てる！　大丈夫か？
Are you all right?
Hurry! Tend her wounds!
（リーンの父）早く傷の手当てを！
She's conscious!
（侍女）あっ 気がつきましたわ！
Rean! Rean!
（リーンの父）リーン…
リーン！　しっかりするんだ
Hang in there!
Her name's Rean, huh?
You're okay now.
（グーグー）
あの子 リーンっていうんだ
（リーンの父）
もう大丈夫だ
H-Help me carry her!
（グーグー）
あの子 リーンっていうんだ
抱えるのを手伝ってくれ
Right!
Ready? and...
Thank goodness. She's safe.
（運転手）はい
（リーンの父）せーの！
よかった 助かったのか
（力み声）
Thank goodness.
Sir...
よかった…
（侍女）旦那さま…
Let's go back to the mansion.
（リーンの父）
いいから 屋敷へ戻ろう
You, hurry home!
君 先に戻っていてくれ
Yes, sir!
（侍女）はい！
（グーグー）ん… つっ…
ハァ…
Where am I?
ここは？
うわ…
I feel sluggish.
体が重い
My belly's sticking out.
なんか… 腹が すごい出てる
あ！
My eyes...
目が… 口が… 鼻が…
My mouth...
My nose...
I look like...
これじゃあ まるで…
Your nose was destroyed, but you can still eat.
（酒爺）鼻は壊れたがメシは食える
I'm surprised you hung in there,
considering what you went through.
あの状態から よくがんばったよ
You're a lucky one.
お前は運がいい！
I always dreamed of living
as someone who wasn't me.
（グーグー）ずっと
僕以外の誰かのように
生きることを夢見ていた
My dream came true.
夢は かなった
I became some kind of monster that isn't me.
僕は僕でない怪物になってしまった
Did you hear?
（店番）知ってるか？
あの変人ジジイ
That freaky old man finally made a monster.
ついに怪物を
作り出したらしいぞ
Hey! Where's the old man?!
（ピオラン）
おい！　ジジイおるか？
Be grateful! Pioran here
has brought a gift for you!
このピオランが お前のために
土産を持ってきてやったぞ
An immortal freak!
不死身の怪物じゃ
Well? Isn't it amazing?
（ピオラン）
どうじゃ すごいじゃろ
And it's immortal, huh?
加えて不死身ときたか
You got me.
参った！　俺の手に余る素材だよ
This is way too much for me.
Where did you even find it, old lady?
一体どこで手に入れたんだ
バアさんよ
The Yanome captured it.
ヤノメが捕らえておった
We went through a lot together,
and now it's with me.
いろいろあって連れ回しとる
H-Hey.
（グーグー）や… やあ
I... My name is Gugu. I'm a servant here.
僕…
俺 ここの使用人で
グーグーっていうんだ
What's your name?
君の名前は？
Name...?
（フシ）な ま…
His name's Fushi.
こいつはフシというんじゃ
Fushi? Because you're immortal?
（グーグー）不死身だからフシ？
That's so on-the-nose!
そのまんまじゃん！　アハハ…
Huh?
は？
You're so weird.
ヘンなヤツだな まあいいか
Well, whatever.
Hey, Booze Man, you mind
if I show him around?
ねえ 酒爺
この人を案内してもいい？
Sure.
ああ
You two are staying here, too, huh?
（グーグー）
君らも ここで過ごすんだって？
I've been here for three months now.
俺 ここに来て３か月たつんだ
I got hurt real bad,
and Booze Man came and helped me.
ひどいケガしたときに
酒爺が助けてくれて
He's a weird old coot.
基本 ヘンな人なんだけどね
Oh, I call him Booze Man
because he makes liquor.
あっ 酒爺ってのは
爺さんが
お酒を造ってるからなんだ
He doesn't have too many customers
because it's such an acquired taste.
マニアにしか受けなくて
客は少ないけど
Look. This is where he does the distilling.
ほら ここで蒸留してるんだよ
What?
ナニ？
（グーグー）ん？
What's "liquor"?
さけ… ナニ？
Oh.
（グーグー）ああ…
Try it.
（グーグー）飲んでみな
（むせる声）
（グーグー）ハハハハ！
I just noticed your clothes are pretty filthy.
そういえば お前
薄汚れた服 着てるよな
People don't like dirty guys.
不潔はモテないぞ
Hey, where are you going?
（酒爺）おい どこ行くんだ？
We're going to play in the water.
（グーグー）
ちょっと水遊びしてくる
ん？
What's wrong?
どうしたの？
You're afraid of the forest, aren't you?
（ピオラン）
森が怖いんじゃろ お前？
Afraid?
（グーグー）怖い？
We were attacked by something
unknown in the forest.
森で得体の知れないヤツに
襲われたんじゃ
It looked just like a tree.
そいつは木に そっくりじゃった
Huh...
（グーグー）へえ…
不死身のくせに本当に怖いの？
You're afraid of it even
though you're immortal?
I'm scared.
こわい
All right. That's fine.
（グーグー）そうか 分かったよ
I'm scared.
（フシ）こ… わい
We'll get in trouble for using this water, but...
（グーグー）
ここの水 使うと怒られるけど
Oh, well.
まあいいや… あれ？
Huh?
Why are you wounded?
なんでケガしてるの？
不死身のくせに
I thought you were immortal.
Do you not know?
分からないのか？
When you don't know how to
answer, you say, "I don't know."
答えが浮かばないときは
“分からない”って言うんだ
I don't know.
（フシ）わからない
Hey, at least you're easy to reason with.
（グーグー）
おっ 聞き分けはいいな
Okay, get undressed.
さあ 脱いで 洗うから
I'll wash it.
Huh?
あれ？　くっついてらぁ…
It's stuck to you.
This, too.
ここも…
And this! Why?!
こっちも！　なんで？
（フシ）んっ
（グーグー）え？
Hey! Don't!
おい よせ！
（フシの力み声）
I don't need to undress!
俺は いいんだよ ブサイクだから…
I'm really ugly!
あ…
See? Aren't I ugly?
ほらな ブサイクだろ？
S-Say something.
（フシ）ん～
（グーグー）な… 何か言えよ
What's "ugly"?
ナニ？
ブサイク
A face that's funny to look at.
（グーグー）見ると
おもしろくなる顔ってことさ
I'm like a monster.
まるで怪物さ
People like me have to
spend our lives in hiding.
俺みたいなヤツは
一生 隠れて過ごすんだ
I understand that, but I still
haven't gotten used to this life.
分かっちゃいるけど
まだ慣れないよ この生活には
Ugly.
（フシ）ブサイク
（グーグー）がっ…
Well, we're both monsters.
Let's stick together.
（グーグー）
まあ 怪物同士 仲良くやろうぜ
Ugly.
（フシ）ブサイク
Listen up, Fushi.
（グーグー）いいか フシ
Since you're going to be living here,
you need to learn the work.
お前は これから
ここで生きていくうえで
必要な仕事を学ばなければならない
（フシ）ん～
Damn it.
（グーグー）ったく！
At least say "yes" or something.
“はい！”とか何とか言え
返事は人間の基本だ
If you're going to be human,
you have to learn to reply.
Yes.
Good.
はい
（グーグー）よし
First thing in the morning when
you wake up, you do cleaning.
（グーグー）
まずは朝起きたら掃除だ
Yes.
Then you cook.
（フシ）はい
（グーグー）次は食事作り
Yes.
（フシ）はい
Work the fields until noon.
After that, we man the shop.
（グーグー）
昼まで畑仕事 午後は店番！
Yes.
はい
So, Fushi, you're bigger than me...
（グーグー）フシって
俺よりデカいけど何歳なの？
How old are you?
I don't know.
わからない
You don't know anything about yourself, huh?
（グーグー）お前 自分のこと
何にも分かんないのな
What about your parents, then?
じゃあ 親は？
顔は知ってるのか？
Do you know what they look like?
I don't know.
わからない “おや” ナニ？
What's a p-parent?
That's where we have to start?
（グーグー）そこからか…
A parent is someone who loves you
unconditionally and cares for you.
親ってのは無条件の愛で自分に
尽くしてくれる人のことだよ
What about siblings?
（グーグー）兄弟は？
一緒に育った人はいたの？
Did you grow up with anyone?
I don't know.
わからない
I had someone.
（グーグー）俺にはいたよ
カッコいい兄ちゃんがね
An awesome older brother.
He's out making money right now.
今 出稼ぎに行っててさ
He's going to come home rich someday.
そのうち お金持ちになって
帰ってくるんだ
I guess you're lucky that
you don't know, in a way.
知らないというのは
ある意味 幸せなのかもな
You don't have to lose hope.
絶望しなくて済む
I envy you.
お前が うらやましいよ
So, what are we doing about him from now on?
（ピオラン）で 今後こいつを
どうすればいいんじゃ？
I'm just a brewer.
What do you want me to tell you?
（酒爺）んなこと
酒屋の俺に聞かれてもね…
He's too much of a rarity
for the world to see.
こんな珍しいヤツ 世間に
知られたら戦(いくさ)が起こるだろうし
It'll start a war.
（フシ）
ウマい ウマい…
I don't know.
（グーグー）そうかな？
Even if it came to that, I'd protect him first.
だとしても そうなる前に
俺が守るけどな
Yum.
（フシ）ウマい ウマい
There must be plenty of people out there
who'd buy him off us for lots of money!
確かに こやつなら
高値で買いたがるヤツが
わんさか おるじゃろうな
Stop it! Don't talk about selling Fushi!
（グーグー）やめてよ！
フシを売るなんて
I know!
分かったぞ
Let's make immortality wine!
不老不死の酒を造ろう
I'll chop off his fingers to make the base!
こやつの指を切り落として
Don't say that, Booze Man!
（グーグー）何言ってるの 酒爺！
勘弁してよ
Give me a break!
アハハハ…
What are you so upset about?
にゃに怒っとるんだい
冗談だろに まじめボーイ
I'm just kidding. You're such a serious boy.
Oh, fine, then.
（ピオラン）しゃあない
大道芸の小銭稼ぎで我慢するかの
Let's just have him make some side
money being a street performer.
（グーグー）むむむ…
Indeed!
（酒爺）そうじゃの ホヘヘ…
Why are you two so greedy?!
（グーグー）２人とも なんで
そんなに欲深いんだよ！
We're not using Fushi to
make money! That's barbaric!
お金のために
フシを利用するなんて野蛮だ
Listen!
いいかい？
Fushi has a precious power.
フシは何ものにも代えがたい
力を持ってる
We ought to be glad that we got to meet him!
そんな彼に出会えたことを
僕らは素直に感謝すべきだ！
I want him to be part of our family!
僕はフシを家族として
迎え入れたいって思ってる！
ん？　そう… フシはまるで兄弟
Right.
He's like a brother.
Your older brother?
お前の兄さんか？
Younger brother!
（グーグー）弟だ！
Yum. Yum.
（フシ）ウマい ウマい…
Hey, what do you think you'll
be doing in ten years?
（グーグー）ねえ
フシは10年後に
自分が どうなってると思う？
I don't understand.
（フシ）いみ わからない
I think I'll still be living like I am now.
（グーグー）
俺は ずっと今みたいな―
生活してるだろうなって思うね
Cleaning, cooking, work...
掃除 炊事 仕事…
A boring life.
退屈な毎日
Before I turned out like this,
俺 こうなる前は
大きな屋敷に住んで
I always dreamed of living in a big
mansion and eating a bellyful every day.
毎日 山盛りのゴハンを食べて
暮らすことを夢見てた
That dream came true.
今 その夢は かなった
But it came at a cost.
でも それには対価があったんだ
My life, where I had a cool big brother
and got to talk with the girl I liked...
カッコいい兄貴がいて
好きな女の子と話している俺の…
My very own life... is never coming back.
俺だけの人生は
もう戻ってこない 二度と…
Not ever.
My future's set in stone now.
これは もう絶対 確定した未来だ
That makes me so miserable.
俺には これが心底つらくてさ
Yum.
（フシ）ウマい
But thanks to you being here, I think
I can put up with this boring life.
でもフシが来てくれた おかげで
この退屈な毎日とも
うまく つきあえそうだよ
So, anyway...
If you were to turn into, say, Booze Man,
would you think booze tastes good?
（グーグー）でさ たとえば
お前が もし酒爺に変化したら
酒をウマいと感じるのかな？
I don't know.
わからない
Try it out, man.
（グーグー）
ちょっと試してみろよ
How?
どうやって？
Pardon me.
（リーン）ごめんください
Yes?! Welcome!
（グーグー）
あ… はい いらっしゃいませ！
Wh-What brings you here today?
きょ… 今日は何のご用で？
This is a brewery, you know.
あの… ここ 酒屋ですが…
Huh?
あ… えっ あの…
Um... I'm not here to try liquor or anything!
別に お酒を
飲みたいわけじゃないの！
I'm looking for something healthy!
体にいいものを探してて
W-We do have supplemental drinks, but...
（グーグー）じ… 滋養を
高めるような薬酒ならあるけど…
Oh, I know!
ああ そうだ！
Shall I bring you some of our
non-alcoholic sweet pickles?
お酒の入ってない甘漬けでも
ご用意しましょうか
They're tasty when cut with water and citrus.
水と柑橘(かんきつ)で割ると おいしいですよ
That sounds fantastic!
す… すてきね！
Will that heal my wound?
それで傷が治るのかしら？
Your wound?
（グーグー）傷？
My wound from three months
ago still hasn't healed.
３か月前にケガした傷口が
まだ治らなくて…
It's a really big, embarrassing wound,
so I have to hide it.
すごく大きな傷で恥ずかしいから
隠すしかないの
L-Let's get that wound fixed!
（グーグー）
な… 治しましょう その傷 絶対！
For sure!
Okay!
S-So cute!
はい！
（グーグー）か… かわいい！
I'm glad this turned out to
be such a friendly shop.
結構 気さくな お店で安心したわ
I thought it'd be a really scary place.
私 てっきり怖い所だと
思っていたの
I mean, what's up with your head thing?
だって その かぶりもの…
一体 何なんですか？
（グーグー）う…
Ugly.
It's for attracting customers!
（フシ）ブサイク…
（グーグー）いやあ 客引きですよ
People love this!
こいつが評判よくって
Oh, really?
そうなの？　ウフフ…
Help! I'm so happy right now!
（グーグー）
ヤバい すごく幸せだ！
No, be careful.
いや 気をつけろ
身の程を忘れるのは危険だ
Gotta be careful to always know my place.
Hey, you guys aren't from
the family here, are you?
ねえ あなた
ここの子供じゃないわよね？
No. We just work here.
（グーグー）
ええ ここで働いてます！
Oh! So you'll be here whenever I come in?
そう！　じゃあ ここに来れば
いつでも いるのね
Sure!
We work the fields in the morning,
and we're here in the afternoon.
（グーグー）はい！　朝は畑
午後は この店にいます！
May I ask your name?
名前… 聞いていいかな？
つっ… ぼ… 僕は
ぐ… グーグーっていいます
I'm...
My name's G-Gugu.
Not you.
違うわ この人に聞いたの
I was asking him.
That's Fushi.
（２人）フシじゃ
うわー フシさんていうんだ
Fushi-san, huh?
That's a beautiful name.
とっても すてきね
年は？　どこから来たの？
How old are you?
Where are you from?
What do you like to eat?
好きな食べ物は？
He likes everything I make for him.
（グーグー）俺が作った料理なら
何でも好きですよ
Fruits.
クダモノ
Really?! Me, too!
（リーン）そうなの？　私も！
Hey, Fushi!
We're in the middle of work!
（グーグー）おい フシ
仕事中だぞ
Call me Rean.
ねえ リーンって言って
Rean.
リーン
You're wonderful!
ああ！　すてき！
Rean.
Oh, you!
（フシ）リーン リーン…
（リーン）ああ いや～ん…
Rean.
All right!
（グーグー）よしよし そろそろ
爺さんの手伝いでもしてくれ
Go help the old man or something.
You're going to distract the other customers.
ほかの お客さんの邪魔だから
No!
I'd like to go for a walk
with Fushi-san, then.
いや… だったらフシさんと
２人で お散歩したいわ
Then we won't be distracting the
other customers, right, Mr. Shopboy?
それなら邪魔にならないでしょ
店員さん？
No!
Listen! He can't even take
his clothes off without help!
（グーグー）ダメです いいですか
あいつは１人で
服も脱げないような男ですよ
He can hardly even speak. He's like a baby!
言葉も たどたどしい
まるで赤ちゃんだ
He needs education.
ですから教育が必要なんです
He doesn't have time to play!
遊んでるヒマなんてありません！
I could teach him how to talk...
言葉なら私が教えてあげるのに
and how to remove his clothes.
もちろん服の脱ぎ方も…
なんちゃって
Just kidding!
（グーグー）ぐぐぐ…
（足音）
Man lives not only for booze.
人は酒のみに生きるにあらず
（グーグー）ん？
Booze can make a person feel
good and make them happy.
（酒爺）酒を飲めば 人は
気持ちよくなって楽しく過ごせるが
But that's not all that nurtures you.
自分を養ってくれるのは
それだけではない
What are you talking about?
I don't drink booze!
（グーグー）何の話？
僕は お酒 飲まないんだけど！
The time you spend so
dejected is time well spent.
お前が そうやって
落ち込んでいる時間は
It makes you that much more
of a cultivated human being.
お前という人間を
味わい深くしてくれる―
大切な時間だと言っとるんだ
（グーグー）ハッ
Embrace the heartache and
become a good man, Gugu!
思う存分 悩んで いい男になれ
グーグーよ
（グーグーの荒い息）
（グーグー）ふっ くっ…
ん… うぐぐ…
ぐ… ぐ…
フゥ
うくっ…
What are you doing?
ナニ やってるの？
I'm working out.
（グーグー）
トレーニングさ
I'm giving myself something
worth being attracted to.
（グーグー）
俺の取り柄を作ってる
Me, too.
（フシ）
おれ も つくる
You don't need to do that!
（グーグー）お前は
やんなくていいんだよ
Get off!
下りろ！
Go back inside and get some sleep.
お前は部屋でグースカ寝とけ
く… フンッ
What's gotten into Gugu?
（ピオラン）
何じゃ グーグーのヤツ…
Look at him go!
（酒爺）やっとる やっとる
それでこそ男だ
That's a good man.
Become strong, kid.
うむ 強くなるんだぞ
フォフォフォフォ…
（フシ）ハハハ…
（フシと酒爺の笑い声）
（３人の笑い声）
（グーグー）ハァ…
うぐぐ…
Preview
As they live a peaceful life in Takunaha,
（観察者）
タクナハでの穏やかな日常
Gugu and Fushi gradually come
to understand each other better.
グーグーとフシは少しずつ
互いの理解を深めていく
But Gugu discovers a secret
hidden within his body.
しかし―
自分の体に隠された
ある秘密に気づいたグーグー
In his despair, alone,
he confronts his own fate.
失意の中 独り
自分の運命に向き合っていく
Monster Brothers